ALYSSA BARNETT

Full Stack Web Developer

PROFILE

Efficient in Full Stack Web Development. Exceptional experience in the "Front End" aspect of Web development. Built a lengthy and detailed portfolio of apps/websites.

Over four (5) years of customer service experience in restaurant and retail settings. Highly motivated, able to multi-task and prioritize workload under pressure, as well as increase pace as workload demands. Excellent interpersonal skills, with ability to build rapport and develop regular clientele. Keen attention to detail. Outstanding knowledge on drawing customers in for business.

CONTACT

PHONE: (704)-728-5718 WEBSITE:

https://github.com/alyssabarnett06 LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/alyssabarnett-a3651213a/

EMAIL:

ca.barnett06@amail.com

Other Skills:

- Experience with node.js, MySQL, and C++
- Quickly identify and resolve problems
- Listen and respond to requests, following up to assure complete satisfaction
- Excellent marketing/ promoting experience
- Highly experienced with Microsoft

EDUCATION

University of North Carolina at Charlotte

[October 8th, 2019 – April 4th, 2020] [Full Stack Web Development Coding Bootcamp Completed]

WORK EXPERIENCE

[Brixx Wood Fired Pizza] [Bartender]

[08/2018 - Present]

[Greeting customers and giving exceptional service in order to make their visit outstanding and to ensure they will be back.]

[RJ Corman Railroad Group] [Train Staff]

[07/2017-08/2018]

[Served customers lunch and dinner on their 2 hour train excursion. Handled money, and company events.]

[Bottle Cap Group] [Server/ Certified Trainer]

[11/2015-07/2017]

[Served guest with outstanding service and trained new employees.]

[Trilogix Golf] [Social Media Manager]

[03/2014-08/2016]

[Handled social media accounts for Trilogix Golf.]

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- Jauery
- React